export const quizQuestions_3 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Which array method is used to create a new array with the results of calling a provided function on every element in the array?',
      choices: ['.forEach()', '.map()', '.filter()', '.reduce()'],
      correctAnswer: '.map()',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does the .filter() method do in ReactJS?',
      choices: ['Creates a new array with elements that pass a test provided by a function', 'Executes a provided function once for each array element', 'Reduces an array to a single value', 'Finds the first element that satisfies a provided condition'],
      correctAnswer: 'Creates a new array with elements that pass a test provided by a function',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which array method returns the first element in an array that satisfies a provided testing function?',
      choices: ['.find()', '.filter()', '.reduce()', '.forEach()'],
      correctAnswer: '.find()',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does the .map() method return?',
      choices: ['A new array with transformed elements', 'A boolean indicating if the provided function returns true for any element', 'The original array with updated elements', 'A single value based on the provided function'],
      correctAnswer: 'A new array with transformed elements',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which method is used to iterate through an array in React and executes a provided function for each element?',
      choices: ['.find()', '.map()', '.filter()', '.forEach()'],
      correctAnswer: '.forEach()',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the primary purpose of the .filter() method in React?',
      choices: ['To create a new array with filtered elements based on a condition', 'To transform elements of the array', 'To find the index of a particular element', 'To concatenate two arrays'],
      correctAnswer: 'To create a new array with filtered elements based on a condition',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which method is used to test whether at least one element in the array passes the provided function?',
      choices: ['.find()', '.some()', '.reduce()', '.map()'],
      correctAnswer: '.some()',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does the .find() method return if no element satisfies the condition?',
      choices: ['null', 'undefined', 'An empty array', 'Throws an error'],
      correctAnswer: 'undefined',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does the .filter() method return if no element satisfies the condition?',
      choices: ['null', 'undefined', 'An empty array', 'Throws an error'],
      correctAnswer: 'An empty array',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which method is used to return a single value after reducing the array elements with a provided function?',
      choices: ['.reduce()', '.map()', '.filter()', '.find()'],
      correctAnswer: '.reduce()',
    },
  ],
};
